MATT GREEN

(845) 558-2377 migreen498@gmail.com 217 Harvard Street 2, Brookline MA

JOB EXPERIENCES

MINTZ

Web Content Specialist

Summer 2019 - Present

- Create and maintain Firm-wide website content across the Mintz environments
- Build creative, engaging, and user-friendly landing pages
- Liasion with front-end users and IT to ticket and conduct website upgrades, bug fixes, and improvements
- Train users on website functionality and best practices

ROAD SCHOLAR

Digital Content Writer

Fall 2017 - Summer 2019

- Research and write long-form SEO content pages
- Update and improve website content and metadata quality
- Support the Digital Designer, creating and publishing email content
- Assist the Writing Ream with writing program copy and editing print publications

Marketing Writer

Fall 2016 - Fall 2017

- Edit copy for print publications reaching hundreds of thousands of households
- Manage multiple projects and deadlines working within the Marketing and Programs departments
- Help create SEO content for the company website
- Primary copywriter for the Adventures Afloat product line

Junior Program Department Writer Winter 2015 - Fall 2016

EDUCATION

UNIVERSITY OF DELAWARE

B.A. in European History

Class of 2014

ABOUT ME

I am a digital marketing professional with six years of experience in copywriting, SEO optimization, website design, and website content management across both creative and technology teams. I am seeking a front-end content focused position in which I can continue to grow and challenge myself.

SKILLS

Microsoft Office
Word, Excel, PowerPoint
Creative Suite:
InCopy, Photoshop, Illustrator,
Dreamweaver
Search Engine Optimization
Google Analytics
HTML, CSS, JavaScript
GitHub, JIRA
Drupal, Squarespace
Creative Thinking, Writing, Editing

CERTIFICATIONS

Learning to Write Marketing Copy - Lynda.com

Inbound Marketing - Hubspot

Content Marketing - HubSpot